picsearch.com 2018-09-04

# Picsearch - Image Search for pictures and images

**Privacy Policy**

This policy is intended to clarify our commitment to protecting your privacy, as well to be sure that you are comfortable with the steps we have taken to provide a satisfactory experience in using Picsearch. This statement explains our current information gathering process, which is subject to change without notice. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy from time to time to update yourself on any such changes.

**Collection and Use of Information**

**Log Files** Picsearch uses log files. These files include IP (internet protocol) addresses, browser identification, platform identification, referring and/or exit pages, time/date stamps, and the number of clicks. IP addresses are obfuscated to not include personally identifiable information. These logs are used to analyze browsing trends, track users' movements in the aggregate, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, and administer the site.

**Customer Service** We maintain regular communication with users in order to provide requested services, or in regard to any account-related issues. These are handled by email or phone, in accordance with the individual user's wishes.

**Information Sharing**

**Disclaimer** While Picsearch makes every effort to protect user privacy, we may be required by law to disclose information when we have a good-faith belief that such information is necessary in order to be in compliance with a court order, legal process or current judicial proceeding involving our website.

**Aggregate (Non-personally Identifiable Information)** We share aggregated demographic information with our advertisers and partners. This information includes page views, browser types, unique visitors, and additional broad demographic data. This data is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**Third-Party Advertisers** Picsearch shares site usage data about its users with reputable third-party advertisers. While we make every effort to accept only advertisers who are reputable, and who share our commitment to privacy protection, we cannot be held responsible for the privacy policies of any advertiser, promotional link, sponsor, or any other third party. Users are advised to check the individual privacy policies for any third-party sites they may visit.

**External Links**  
Picsearch contains links to external websites. Picsearch is not responsible for the privacy policies of these external sites. We advise all users to be aware when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of every website that collects personally identifiable information.
